bewellbuzz.com 2013-05-03

# privacy policy | Be Well Buzz

At BeWellBuzz.com we appreciate your readership and value your personal privacy. We respect the personal nature of the information you provide us on our web site and acknowledge the importance of protecting this information. In adopting this privacy policy, our intent is to balance our legitimate business interests in collecting and using your personal information with your reasonable expectations of privacy. The policy may be revised or updated at any time and we encourage you to check back often to ensure that you are familiar with the most recent version and the terms of our policy.

### When does BeWellBuzz.com collect my personal information?

You may provide personal information to BeWellBuzz.com in one of four ways: (1) by sharing your e-mail address and subscribing to email newsletters or requesting site updates, (2) by sharing personal information when you provide tips to our news department, (3) by sharing personal information when you post comments on our posts or stories, or (4) by sharing contact information as a Contagious Festival entrant. We may also ask for other information at other times but at no time will you be required to share any personal information to gain complete access to our site.

In addition to personal information—such as name, street and e-mail addresses, and telephone numbers—we may also collect information that is in no way personally identifiable. This may include the operating system you are working on, the internet browser you are using, the domain name of your internet service provider, and the web sites you visit directly before and after your visit to BeWellBuzz.com.

### How does BeWellBuzz.com use my personal information?

The more we know about you, the better we are able to customize our web site to suit your personal preferences and interests. The e-mail address you provide may be used by BeWellBuzz.com for any reason, such as contacting you for editorial purposes or to advise you of any changes to our site. We may also from time to time send you messages about our marketing partners’ products.

To maintain a site that is free of charge and does not require registration, we display advertisements on our web site. We also use the information you give us to help our advertisers target the audience they want to reach. At no time does any party other than BeWellBuzz.com have access to your personally identifiable information, and you will never be contacted by any party other than BeWellBuzz.com. The only exceptions to the foregoing are that we may disclose personally identifiable information (i) in response to legal process, for example, in response to a court order or subpoena, (ii) in response to a law enforcement agency’s request, or where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take actions regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of another person, violations of our terms of use, or as otherwise required by law, or (iii) in the event we are acquired by or merged with another company.

When you sign up for our updates or receive e-mail messages from BeWellBuzz.com, you will always be given the chance to opt-out of special offers and site updates. You may change your preferences at any time and will only be contacted in manners consistent with your stated preferences.

Non-personally identifiable information (such as stated above) may be shared in aggregate form with our advertisers or marketing partners but your personally identifiable information will never be disclosed to them.

### Is there anything else I should know about my privacy and BeWellBuzz.com?

Any information you disclose voluntarily on our comments pages or in any forums we may develop in the future becomes public information. We cannot control the actions of our site users and advise you to use your discretion in sharing information about yourself on the internet. All information sharing is optional and done so at your own risk. Privacy is a very personal matter and we encourage you to be careful and responsible when disclosing personal information online.

(revised 12.15.2010)

### [BeWellBuzz](http://www.bewellbuzz.com/author/Buzz%20Team/ "BeWellBuzz")

The mission and goal of this site is to provide you with scientifically researched natural health and personal development information. Natural health & personal development advocates Larry Oz & his wife Oksana seek to awaken people to their highest levels of personal truth. They work tirelessly to inspire you to elevate your spirit, do more, live better, and think deeper one day at a time. When you like and share this information, you help make the world a better place. As always, please seek professional advice before implementing any recommendations. BeWellBuzz.com is brought to you by [Halcyon Publishing](http://www.halcyonpublishing.net/). Check out our magazine by [clicking here](https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/be-well-buzz-magazine/id577503787?ls=1&mt=8).

[More Posts](http://www.bewellbuzz.com/author/Buzz%20Team/ "More posts by BeWellBuzz") \- [Website](http://www.bewellbuzz.com/ "BeWellBuzz")

Follow Me:
